zendetv.com 2019-07-18

# Cookie and Privacy Policy - Zende TV

**Privacy Policy for www.zendetv.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us [here](http://www.zendetv.com/contact).

At www.zendetv.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by www.zendetv.com and how we use it.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.zendetv.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**What information do we collect (data collection)?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
Other than described in this privacy policy, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, third party marketers, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.zendetv.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements  
**Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

If you have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=94152), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy as well in the following manner.

Users Information [http://zendetv.com](http://zendetv.com/) does not store any of your personal information. Third Party Sites In order to optimize your visit, http://zendetv.com  supports ads from third party sites. These sites may collect information such as your domain type or your IP address. For further information on these sites, please consult the privacy policies of the following: valueclickmedia, Nabbr , adbrite, burst media, and underdogmedia. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, contact us.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie  
**→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.zendetv.com.  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to www.zendetv.com and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Our Advertising Partners  
**Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google
  * DoubleClick
  * Taboola

These third-party ad zendes or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.zendetv.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

www.zendetv.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Party Privacy Policies  
**You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad zendes for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.bebinfa.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Children’s Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. www.zendetv.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that www.zendetv.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**Online Privacy Policy Only (data sharing)**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Monday, May 25th, 2018.  
_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._
